For my first define function, it stores user’s new inputs of name, address, phone number, email address into the list containing all contacts.
For my second define function, it prints the list that contains all contact information. By using for loop, it joins all of the contact information in the contacts list until everything is printed. 
For my third define function, it searches for the contact that user inputs and print everything that is found. By using count, it helps determine if there is a match found while searching. If there is no contact information, then it will print that no contact is found. 
For my fourth define function, it modifies the contact information, which user enters the information(name, address, phone number, email) they want to modify, and then input the updated information. The counter also helps determine if there is a match found while searching through the contact list. 
For my fifth define function, user inputs the name that they want to remove, and it will search through the contact list. Once the name was found, then it will delete the list if searched name has a match with user’s input.
My main function basically shows the address book menu for user to choose first to edit their contact information. Further, it will combine all the previous define function and conduct a input validation. 